Guide to the Richard Charles Lee Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Mayoral Files, 1943-1969; Series I; 44 linear feet (106 boxes)
  - 1960
    - "R" general (Box 36, Folder 786)
    - Redevelopment: Appleby, L. Thomas (Box 36, Folder 787)
    - Redevelopment: bids for work (Box 36, Folder 788)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street (Box 36, Folder 789-790)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Project (Box 36, Folder 791)
    - Redevelopment: Logue, Edward J. (Box 37, Folder 792)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 37, Folder 793)
    - Redevelopment: Middle Ground (Box 37, Folder 794-795)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 796-799)
    - Redevelopment: Mulligan, George (Box 37, Folder 800)
    - Redevelopment: Oak Street Connector (Box 37, Folder 801)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, business (Box 37, Folder 802)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, housing (Box 37, Folder 803)
    - Redevelopment: South Boulevard (Box 37, Folder 804)
    - Redevelopment: Whitney Avenue Fire Station (Box 37, Folder 805)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 37, Folder 806-807)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square Co-op (Box 37, Folder 808)
    - Redevelopment: University Towers (Box 38, Folder 809)
    - Republican Party (Box 38, Folder 810)
    - Retirement, city employees (Box 38, Folder 811)
    - "S" general (Box 38, Folder 812-814)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 38, Folder 815)
    - "I" general (Box 38, Folder 816)
    - Tax Office (Box 38, Folder 817)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 38, Folder 818-823)
    - "U" general (Box 38, Folder 824)
    - Unions (Box 38, Folder 825)
    - United Illuminating Company (Box 38, Folder 826)
    - "V" general (Box 39, Folder 827)
    - Veterans (Box 39, Folder 828)
    - Voters, Registrar of (Box 39, Folder 829)
    - "W" general (Box 39, Folder 830)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 39, Folder 831-836)
    - Welfare, Department of: Senior Citizens Center (Box 39, Folder 837)
    - Welfare, Department of: Springside Home (Box 39, Folder 838)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 39, Folder 839)
    - Yale University (Box 39, Folder 840-841)
    - Zoning Board (Box 39, Folder 842)
  - 1961
    - "A" general (Box 39, Folder 843)
    - Administration (Box 40, Folder 844-846)
    - Administration: circuit court (Box 40, Folder 847)
    - Airport (Box 40, Folder 848-854)
    - Airport (helioport) (Box 40, Folder 855)
    - Aldermen, Board of (Box 40, Folder 856)
    - "B" general (Ba-Bo) (Box 40, Folder 857-858)
    - "B" general (Br-By) (Box 41, Folder 859)
    - Berlin trip (Box 41, Folder 860-862)
    - Building Department (Box 41, Folder 863)
    - Bus Terminal (proposed) (Box 41, Folder 864)
    - Bush, Prescott (Box 41, Folder 865)
    - "C" general (Box 41, Folder 866-867)
    - Cabinet meetings (Box 41, Folder 868)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 41, Folder 869)
    - Charter (Box 41, Folder 870)
    - Citizens Action Commission: general (Box 41, Folder 871)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Jepson, Alan H. (Box 41, Folder 872)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Progress Pavilion (Box 41, Folder 873)
    - City Clerk (Box 41, Folder 874)
    - City Plan (Box 41, Folder 875)
    - City Plan: Andrews, Norris (Box 42, Folder 876)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission (Box 42, Folder 877)
    - Code of ethics (Box 42, Folder 878)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 42, Folder 879)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 42, Folder 880)
    - Controller (Box 42, Folder 881)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 42, Folder 882)
    - Council of Social Agencies (Box 42, Folder 883)
    - Cronin, William J. (Box 42, Folder 884)
    - "D" general (Box 42, Folder 885)
    - Democratic Party (Box 42, Folder 886)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 42, Folder 887)
    - "E" general (Box 42, Folder 888)
    - Education: candidates for jobs (Box 42, Folder 889)
    - Education: Sargent Survey (Box 42, Folder 890)
    - Education, Department of: general (Box 42, Folder 891)
    - Education, Department of: general (Box 43, Folder 892-894)
    - Education, Department of: high schools (Box 43, Folder 895)
    - Engineering Department (Box 43, Folder 896)
    - "F" general (Box 43, Folder 897)
    - Feriola, Peter (Box 43, Folder 898)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 43, Folder 899)
    - Fire Department (Box 43, Folder 900)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 43, Folder 901)
    - "G" general (Box 43, Folder 902)
    - Golden; John M. (Box 43, Folder 903)
    - "H" general (Box 43, Folder 904)
    - Harcourt, Brace & Co. (Box 43, Folder 905)
    - Health, Department of (Box 43, Folder 906)
    - Health, Department of: Environmental Sanitation (Box 43, Folder 907)
    - Housing (Box 43, Folder 908)
    - Housing (Box 44, Folder 909-910)
    - Housing: Eastview (Box 44, Folder 911)
    - Housing: proposed Whitney Avenue Station (Box 44, Folder 912)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 44, Folder 913)
    - Human Relations Advisor (Box 44, Folder 914)
    - "I" general (Box 44, Folder 915)
    - "J" general (Box 44, Folder 916)
    - "L" general (Box 44, Folder 917)
    - Legal Aid Bureau (Box 44, Folder 918)
    - "Mac" general (Box 44, Folder 919)
    - "M" general (Box 44, Folder 920)
    - "N" general (Box 44, Folder 921)
    - N. A. A. C. P. (Box 44, Folder 922)
    - Neighborhood improvement program (Box 44, Folder 923)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company (Box 45, Folder 924)
    - Nuclear Research Center (Box 45, Folder 925)
    - "O" general (Box 45, Folder 926)
    - "P" general (Box 45, Folder 927)
    - Park Department (Box 45, Folder 928-930)
    - Passett, Barry (Box 45, Folder 931)
    - Police Department: animal shelter (Box 45, Folder 932)
    - Public Works, Department of (Box 45, Folder 933-934)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 45, Folder 935)
    - "Q" general (Box 45, Folder 936)
    - "R" general (Box 45, Folder 937)
    - Redevelopment: Appleby, L. Thomas (Box 45, Folder 938)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street (Box 46, Folder 939-940)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street Extension (Box 46, Folder 941)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Avenue (Box 46, Folder 942)
    - Redevelopment: Logue, Edward J. (Box 46, Folder 943)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 46, Folder 944)
    - Redevelopment: Madison Towers (Box 46, Folder 945)
    - Redevelopment: Medical-Dental Center (Box 46, Folder 946)
    - Redevelopment: Middle Ground (Box 46, Folder 947)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 948-950)
    - Redevelopment: Mulligan, George (Box 46, Folder 951)
    - Redevelopment: Oak Street Connector (Box 46, Folder 952)
    - Redevelopment: other cities (Box 46, Folder 953)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, business (Box 46, Folder 954)
    - Redevelopment: relocation, housing (Box 46, Folder 955)
    - Redevelopment: Route 5 (Box 46, Folder 956)
    - Redevelopment: South Boulevard (Box 46, Folder 957)
    - Redevelopment: University Towers (Box 47, Folder 958)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 47, Folder 959-960)
    - Regional Planning Agency of South Central Connecticut (Box 47, Folder 961)
    - Republican Party (Box 47, Folder 962)
    - Retarded Children (Box 47, Folder 963)
    - Retirement: city employees (Box 47, Folder 964)
    - "S" general (Box 47, Folder 965-967)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 47, Folder 968)
    - "T" general (Box 47, Folder 969)
    - Tax office (Box 47, Folder 970)
    - Town Clerk (Box 47, Folder 971)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 47, Folder 972-973)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 48, Folder 974-975)
    - Training Program (Box 48, Folder 976)
    - "U" general (Box 48, Folder 977)
    - Unions (Box 48, Folder 978)
    - United Illuminating Company (Box 48, Folder 979)
    - "V" general (Box 48, Folder 980)
    - Veterans (Box 48, Folder 981)
    - "W" general (Box 48, Folder 982-983)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 48, Folder 984-985)
    - Welfare, Department of: senior center (Box 48, Folder 986)
    - Welfare, Department of: Springside Home (Box 48, Folder 987)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 48, Folder 988)
    - Yale University (Box 49, Folder 989-990)
    - Zoning Board (Box 49, Folder 991)
  - 1962
    - "A" general (Box 49, Folder 992)
    - Administration (Box 49, Folder 993-995)
    - Airport (Box 49, Folder 996-997)
    - "B" general (Box 49, Folder 998-999)
    - Budget (Box 49, Folder 1000)
    - Building Department (Box 49, Folder 1001)
    - "C" general (Box 50, Folder 1002-1003)
    - Charter (Box 50, Folder 1004)
    - Citizens Action Commission: general (Box 50, Folder 1005-1006)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Jepson, Alan H. (Box 50, Folder 1007)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Progress Pavilion (Box 50, Folder 1008)
    - City Clerk (Box 50, Folder 1009)
    - City Plan (Box 50, Folder 1010)
    - Citizen Defense (Box 50, Folder 1011)
    - Civil War Centennial Commission (Box 50, Folder 1012)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 50, Folder 1013)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 50, Folder 1014-1015)
    - Controller (Box 50, Folder 1016-1017)
    - CORE (Box 50, Folder 1018)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 50, Folder 1019)
    - Cronin, William J. (Box 50, Folder 1020)
    - "D" general (Box 50, Folder 1021)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 51, Folder 1022)
    - Democratic Party (Box 51, Folder 1023)
    - "E" general (Box 51, Folder 1024)
    - Education, Department of (Box 51, Folder 1025-1027)
    - Education, Department of: high schools (Box 51, Folder 1028)
    - Education, Department of: Sargent Survey (Box 51, Folder 1029)
    - Engineering Department (Box 51, Folder 1030)
    - Ethics, Board of (Box 51, Folder 1031)
    - "F" general (Box 51, Folder 1032)
    - Feriola, Peter (Box 51, Folder 1033)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 51, Folder 1034)
    - Fire Department: Whitney Ave., Lawrence St. (Box 51, Folder 1035)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 51, Folder 1036)
    - Ford Foundation: Community Progress, Inc. (Box 51, Folder 1037-1039)
    - "G" general (Box 52, Folder 1040)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 52, Folder 1041)
    - "H" general (Box 52, Folder 1042)
    - Health, Department of (Box 52, Folder 1043)
    - Hilltop Farm School Foundation (Box 52, Folder 1044)
    - Housing (Box 52, Folder 1045-1046)
    - Housing: Eastview (Box 52, Folder 1047)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 52, Folder 1048)
    - Human Relations Advisor (Box 52, Folder 1049)
    - Human Relations Council (Box 52, Folder 1050)
    - "I" general (Box 52, Folder 1051)
    - "J" general (Box 52, Folder 1052)
    - "K" general (Box 52, Folder 1053)
    - "L" general (Box 52, Folder 1054-1055)
    - Legal Aid Bureau (Box 52, Folder 1056)
    - Library (Box 52, Folder 1057)
    - Lynch, Ed: reports (Box 52, Folder 1058)
    - "Mac" general (Box 52, Folder 1059)
    - "M" general (Box 53, Folder 1060)
    - Macy's (Box 53, Folder 1061)
    - "N" general (Box 53, Folder 1062)
    - N.A. A. C. P. (Box 53, Folder 1063)
    - Neighborhood improvement project (Box 53, Folder 1064)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company (Box 53, Folder 1065)
    - "O" general (Box 53, Folder 1066)
    - "P" general (Box 53, Folder 1067)
    - Park Department (Box 53, Folder 1068-1069)
    - Passett, Barry (Box 53, Folder 1070)
    - Public Works, Department of (Box 53, Folder 1071-1072)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 53, Folder 1073)
    - "Q" general (Box 53, Folder 1074)
    - "R" general (Box 53, Folder 1075)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 53, Folder 1076)
    - Redevelopment: Appleby, L. Thomas (Box 53, Folder 1077)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street Garage (Box 54, Folder 1078)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Project (Box 54, Folder 1079)
    - Redevelopment: Grabino, Harold (Box 54, Folder 1080)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 54, Folder 1081)
    - Redevelopment: Madison Towers (Box 54, Folder 1083)
    - Redevelopment: Medical Center (Box 54, Folder 1084)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 1085-1086)
    - Redevelopment: other cities (Box 54, Folder 1087)
    - Redevelopment: relocation (Box 54, Folder 1088)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 54, Folder 1089)
    - Retarded Children, Association for (Box 54, Folder 1090)
    - Retraining program (Box 54, Folder 1091)
    - "S" general (Box 54, Folder 1092-1093)
    - "T" general (Box 54, Folder 1094)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 55, Folder 1095-1097)
    - U. S. Conference of Mayors (Box 55, Folder 1101)
    - "V" general (Box 55, Folder 1102)
    - "W" general (Box 55, Folder 1103)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 55, Folder 1104)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 55, Folder 1105)
    - Yale University (Box 55, Folder 1106)
    - Zoning Board (Box 55, Folder 1107)
  - 1963
    - "A" general (Box 55, Folder 1108)
    - Administration (Box 55, Folder 1109)
    - Administration (Box 56, Folder 1110)
    - Airport (Box 56, Folder 1111)
    - Airport (helioport) (Box 56, Folder 1112)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 56, Folder 1113)
    - "B" general (Box 56, Folder 1114-1115)
    - Building Department (Box 56, Folder 1116)
    - Bush, Prescott (Box 56, Folder 1117)
    - "C" general (Box 56, Folder 1118-1119)
    - Citizens Action Commission: general (Box 56, Folder 1120)
    - Citizens Action Commission: Jepson, Alan H. (Box 56, Folder 1121)
    - City Planning (Box 56, Folder 1122)
    - Clairol, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 1123)
    - Code of Ethics (Box 56, Folder 1124)
    - Community Progress, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 1125)
    - Community Progress, Inc.: juvenile delinquency (Box 56, Folder 1126)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 57, Folder 1127)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 57, Folder 1128)
    - Controller (Box 57, Folder 1129)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 57, Folder 1130)
    - "D" general (Box 57, Folder 1131-32)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 57, Folder 1133)
    - "E" general (Box 57, Folder 1134)
    - Education, Department of: fifth amendment (Box 57, Folder 1135)
    - Education, Department of: general (Box 57, Folder 1136-1138)
    - Education, Department of: high schools (Box 57, Folder 1139)
    - Education, Department of: Hill School (Box 57, Folder 1140)
    - Engineering Department (Box 57, Folder 1141)
    - "F" general (Box 58, Folder 1142)
    - Feriola, Peter (Box 58, Folder 1143)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 58, Folder 1144)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 58, Folder 1145)
    - "G" general (Box 58, Folder 1146)
    - Gilbert, A. C. Company (Box 58, Folder 1147)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 58, Folder 1148)
    - Grace-New Haven Hospital (Box 58, Folder 1149)
    - "H" general (Box 58, Folder 1150)
    - Harris, Louis (Box 58, Folder 1151)
    - Health, Department of (Box 58, Folder 1152)
    - Housing Authority (Box 58, Folder 1153)
    - Human Rights Committee (Box 58, Folder 1154)
    - "I" general (Box 58, Folder 1155)
    - "J" general (Box 58, Folder 1156)
    - "K" general (Box 58, Folder 1157)
    - Kennedy's death, suggested memorials (Box 59, Folder 1158-1159)
    - "L" general (Box 59, Folder 1160)
    - Legal Aid Bureau (Box 59, Folder 1161)
    - Library (Box 59, Folder 1162)
    - Logue, Edward J. (Box 59, Folder 1163)
    - "Mac" general (Box 59, Folder 1164)
    - "M" general (Box 59, Folder 1165)
    - Macy's (Box 59, Folder 1166)
    - "N" general (Box 59, Folder 1167)
    - N. A. A. C. P. (Box 59, Folder 1168)
    - Neighborhood improvement project (Box 59, Folder 1169)
    - "O" general (Box 59, Folder 1170)
    - "P" general (Box 59, Folder 1171)
    - Park Department (Box 59, Folder 1172)
    - Park Department (Box 60, Folder 1173)
    - Personnel (Box 60, Folder 1174)
    - Public Works Department (Box 60, Folder 1175)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 60, Folder 1176)
    - "Q" general (Box 60, Folder 1177)
    - "R" general (Box 60, Folder 1178)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 60, Folder 1179-1180)
    - Redevelopment: Appleby, L. Thomas (Box 60, Folder 1181-1182)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street (Box 60, Folder 1183-1184)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street Garage (Box 60, Folder 1185)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Project (Box 60, Folder 1186)
    - Redevelopment: Dwight Urban Renewed Project (Box 60, Folder 1187)
    - Redevelopment: Grabino, Harold (Box 61, Folder 1188)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 61, Folder 1189)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 61, Folder 1190-1192)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 61, Folder 1193)
    - Retraining program (Box 61, Folder 1194)
    - "S" general (Box 61, Folder 1195-1196)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 61, Folder 1197)
    - "T" general (Box 61, Folder 1198)
    - Talbot, Allan (Box 61, Folder 1199)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 61, Folder 1200-1201)
    - "U" general (Box 61, Folder 1202)
    - Unions (Box 61, Folder 1203)
    - U. S. Conference of Mayors (Box 61, Folder 1204)
    - U. S. Conference of Mayors: Hawaii (Box 61, Folder 1205)
    - U. S. Conference of Mayors: proceedings (Box 62, Folder 1206)
    - U. S. Government (Box 62, Folder 1207)
    - "V" general (Box 62, Folder 1208)
    - "W" general (Box 62, Folder 1209)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 62, Folder 1210)
    - West River flood control (Box 62, Folder 1211)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 62, Folder 1212)
    - Yale University (Box 62, Folder 1213-1214)
  - 1964
    - "A" general (Box 62, Folder 1215)
    - ACTION (Box 62, Folder 1216)
    - Administration (Box 62, Folder 1217)
    - Airport (Box 62, Folder 1218-1219)
    - Airport (helioport) (Box 62, Folder 1220)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 62, Folder 1221)
    - "B" general (Box 63, Folder 1222)
    - Barbieri, Arthur T. (Box 63, Folder 1223)
    - Bove, Anthony (Box 63, Folder 1224)
    - Brewster Estate (Box 63, Folder 1225)
    - Budget (Box 63, Folder 1226)
    - Building Department (Box 63, Folder 1227)
    - "C" general (Box 63, Folder 1228-1229)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 63, Folder 1230)
    - Citizens Action Commission (Box 63, Folder 1231)
    - City Clerk (Box 63, Folder 1232)
    - City Plan (Box 63, Folder 1233)
    - Code of Ethics (Box 63, Folder 1234)
    - Community Progress, Inc. (Box 63, Folder 1235-1236)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 64, Folder 1237)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 64, Folder 1238)
    - Controller (Box 64, Folder 1239)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 64, Folder 1240)
    - "D" general (Box 64, Folder 1241)
    - Democratic Party (Box 64, Folder 1242)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 64, Folder 1243)
    - "E" general (Box 64, Folder 1244)
    - Education, Department of (Box 64, Folder 1245-1247)
    - Engineering Department (Box 64, Folder 1248)
    - "F" general (Box 64, Folder 1249)
    - Fitzgerald, David E. (Box 64, Folder 1250)
    - Fleming, Robert I. (Box 64, Folder 1251)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 64, Folder 1252)
    - "G" general (Box 64, Folder 1253)
    - Gilbert, A. C., Company (Box 64, Folder 1254)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 64, Folder 1255)
    - "H" general (Box 65, Folder 1256)
    - Health, Department of (Box 65, Folder 1257-1258)
    - Health, Department of: Environmental Sanitation (Box 65, Folder 1259)
    - Housing (Box 65, Folder 1260-1261)
    - Housing Authority (Box 65, Folder 1262)
    - Housing: code enforcement (Box 65, Folder 1263)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 65, Folder 1264)
    - "I" general (Box 65, Folder 1265)
    - "J" general (Box 65, Folder 1266)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (also War on Poverty) (Box 65, Folder 1267)
    - "K" general (Box 65, Folder 1268)
    - Kennedy Library (Box 65, Folder 1269)
    - Kennedy's death, suggested memorials (Box 65, Folder 1270-1271)
    - "L" general (Box 66, Folder 1272)
    - Legal Aid Bureau (Box 66, Folder 1273)
    - Library (Box 66, Folder 1274)
    - "Mac" general (Box 66, Folder 1275)
    - "M" general (Box 66, Folder 1276)
    - MITE Corporation (Box 66, Folder 1277)
    - "N" general (Box 66, Folder 1278)
    - N. A. A. C. P. (CORE) (Box 66, Folder 1279)
    - Neighborhood improvement (Box 66, Folder 1280)
    - "O" general (Box 66, Folder 1281)
    - "P" general (Box 66, Folder 1282-1283)
    - Park Department (Box 66, Folder 1284-1285)
    - Personnel (Box 66, Folder 1286)
    - Public Works Department (Box 67, Folder 1287)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 67, Folder 1288)
    - "Q" general (Box 67, Folder 1289)
    - "R" general (Box 67, Folder 1290)
    - Redevelopment: Adams, Melvin J. (Box 67, Folder 1291)
    - Redevelopment: Appleby, L. Thomas (Box 67, Folder 1292-1293)
    - Redevelopment: Church Street (Box 67, Folder 1294)
    - Redevelopment: Dixwell Project (Box 67, Folder 1295)
    - Redevelopment: Front Block (Box 67, Folder 1296-1297)
    - Redevelopment: Long Wharf (Box 67, Folder 1298)
    - Redevelopment: miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 1299-1300)
    - Redevelopment: Temple Street Garage (Box 68, Folder 1301)
    - Redevelopment: Wooster Square (Box 68, Folder 1302)
    - "S" general (Box 68, Folder 1303-1304)
    - "T" general (Box 68, Folder 1305)
    - Talbot, Allan (Box 68, Folder 1306)
    - Traffic and Parking, Department of (Box 68, Folder 1307-1308)
    - "U" general (Box 68, Folder 1309)
    - Unions (Box 68, Folder 1310)
    - U. S. Conference of Mayors (Box 68, Folder 1311)
    - U. S. Government (Box 68, Folder 1312)
    - "V" general (Box 68, Folder 1313)
    - "W" general (Box 68, Folder 1314)
    - Welfare, Department of (Box 68, Folder 1315)
    - Welfare, Department of: senior center (Box 68, Folder 1316)
    - Welfare, Department of: Springside Home (Box 68, Folder 1317)
    - "XYZ" general (Box 68, Folder 1318)
    - Yale University (Box 68, Folder 1319)
    - Yale University (Box 69, Folder 1320)
  - 1965
    - "A" general (Box 69, Folder 1321)
    - Administration (Box 69, Folder 1322-1323)
    - Airport (Box 69, Folder 1324-1325)
    - Assessors, Board of (Box 69, Folder 1326)
    - "B" general (Box 69, Folder 1327-1329)
    - Bove, Anthony (Box 69, Folder 1330)
    - Brewster Estate (Box 69, Folder 1331)
    - Building Department (Box 69, Folder 1332)
    - "C" general (Box 70, Folder 1333-1335)
    - Carnegie Corporation (Box 70, Folder 1336)
    - Citizens Action Commission (Box 70, Folder 1337)
    - City Plan (Box 70, Folder 1338)
    - Community Progress, Inc. (Box 70, Folder 1339-1340)
    - Connecticut, State of: general (Box 70, Folder 1341)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department (Box 70, Folder 1342)
    - Connecticut, State of: Highway Department, Route 34 and Interstate 91 (Box 70, Folder 1343)
    - Controller (Box 70, Folder 1344)
    - CORE (Box 71, Folder 1345)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 71, Folder 1346)
    - "D" general (Box 71, Folder 1347)
    - Dempsey, John N. (Box 71, Folder 1348)
    - De Vit, George (Box 71, Folder 1349)
    - "E" general (Box 71, Folder 1350)
    - Education, Department of (Box 71, Folder 1351-1355)
    - Education, Department of (Box 72, Folder 1356)
    - Education, Department of; Le Vine, Robert (Box 72, Folder 1357)
    - Einhorn, Joseph J. (Box 72, Folder 1358)
    - Engineering Department (Box 72, Folder 1359)
    - Equal Opportunities Commission (Box 72, Folder 1360)
    - "F" general (Box 72, Folder 1361)
    - Finance, Board of (Box 72, Folder 1362)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 72, Folder 1363)
    - "G" general (Box 72, Folder 1364-1365)
    - Giaimo, Robert N. (Box 72, Folder 1366)
    - Gilbert, A. C., Company (Box 72, Folder 1367)
    - Golden, John M. (Box 72, Folder 1368)
    - "H" general (Box 72, Folder 1369-1370)
    - Health, Department of (Box 72, Folder 1371)
    - Housing (Box 73, Folder 1372)
    - Housing; Federal Housing Agency (Box 73, Folder 1373)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 73, Folder 1374)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 73, Folder 1375)
    - "I" general (Box 73, Folder 1376)
    - "J" general (Box 73, Folder 1377)